<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
  <template id="external_layout_standard_custom">
    <div t-attf-class="header" t-att-style="report_header_style">
      <div class="row">
        <div class="col-12 text-center mt-3">
          <h2>WESTSIDE MARKET</h2>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>

    <div
      t-attf-class="article o_report_layout_standard o_company_#{company.id}_layout {{  'o_layout_background' if company.layout_background in ['Geometric', 'Custom']  else  '' }}"
      t-attf-style="background-image: url({{ 'data:image/png;base64,%s' % company.layout_background_image.decode('utf-8') if company.layout_background_image and company.layout_background == 'Custom' else '/base/static/img/bg_background_template.jpg' if company.layout_background == 'Geometric' else ''}});"
      t-att-data-oe-model="o and o._name" t-att-data-oe-id="o and o.id"
      t-att-data-oe-lang="o and o.env.context.get('lang')">
      <t t-out="0" />
    </div>

    <div t-attf-class="footer o_standard_footer o_company_#{company.id}_layout">
      <div class="text-center" style="border-top: 1px solid black;">
        <ul class="list-inline mb4">
          <div t-field="company.report_footer" />
        </ul>

        <div t-if="report_type == 'pdf'" class="text-muted"> Page: <span class="page" /> / <span
            class="topage" />
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </template>

  <!-- Public api: layout to t-call from reports -->

  <template id="external_layout_custom">
    <t t-if="not o" t-set="o" t-value="doc" />

    <t t-if="not company">
      <!-- Multicompany -->
      <t t-if="company_id">
        <t t-set="company" t-value="company_id" />
      </t>
      <t t-elif="o and 'company_id' in o and o.company_id.sudo()">
        <t t-set="company" t-value="o.company_id.sudo()" />
      </t>
      <t t-else="else">
        <t t-set="company" t-value="res_company" />
      </t>
    </t>

    <t t-call="bmb_templates.external_layout_standard_custom">
      <t t-out="0" />
    </t>

  </template>


  <template id="bmb_templates.bmb_contract">

    <t t-call="web.html_container">
      <t t-call="bmb_templates.external_layout_custom">
        <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="record">
          <t t-set="lang" t-value="doc.partner_id.lang" />
          <div class="page">
            <div class="">
              

                <div class="text-center mb-3">
                  <h4>CONSIGNMENT, DISPLAY &amp; SALES AGREEMENT - MIDTOWN</h4>
                </div>

              <div class="">
                

                <t t-set="member_code" t-value="record.partner_id.member_code or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="create_date" t-value="record.create_date or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="vat" t-value="record.partner_id.vat or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="space_names"
                  t-value="','.join([line.product_id.product_tmpl_id.stock_location_id.name or '' for line in record.order_line]) or '_______________'" />

                <t t-set="company_name" t-value="record.company_id.name or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="amount_total" t-value="record.amount_total or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="years_in_business"
                  t-value="record.partner_id.years_in_business or '___________'" />
                <t t-set="city" t-value="record.partner_id.city or '________'" />
                <t t-set="state_name" t-value="record.partner_id.state_id.name or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="street" t-value="record.partner_id.street or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="zip_code" t-value="record.partner_id.zip or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="mobile" t-value="record.partner_id.mobile or '_______________'" />
                <t t-set="email" t-value="record.partner_id.email or '_______________'" />
                <style>
                  td {
                  padding-left:10px;
                  padding-right:10px;

                  },
                  tr {
                  padding-top:5px;
                  padding-bottom:5px;
                  }
                </style>
                <table >
                  <tr>
                    <td colspan="2">Consignor Code: <u>
                        <t t-esc="member_code" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                    <td colspan="2">Date: <u>
                        <t t-esc="create_date" t-options="{'widget': 'date'}" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                  </tr>
                  <tr height="30px">
                    
                  </tr>
                  <tr>
                    <td colspan="2">Space(s): <u>
                        <t t-esc="space_names" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                    <td colspan="2">Monthly Marketing Fee(s): <u>
                        <t t-esc="amount_total " />$ </u>
                    </td>
                  </tr>
                  <tr height="20px">
                    
                  </tr>
                  <tr>
                    <td colspan="2">First Name: _________________</td>
                    <td colspan="2">Last Name: _________________</td>
                  </tr>
                  <tr height="30px">
                    
                  </tr>
                  <tr>
                    <td colspan="2">Tax ID: <u>
                        <t t-esc="vat" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                    <td colspan="2">Company/Organization Name: <u>
                        <t t-esc="company_name" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                  </tr>
                  
                  <tr height="30px">
                    
                  </tr>
                  <tr>
                    <td colspan="2">Years in Business: <u>
                        <t t-esc="years_in_business" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                    <td colspan="2">Address: <u>
                        <t t-esc="street" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                    <td colspan="2">City: <u>
                        <t t-esc="city" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                  </tr>
                  <tr height="30px">
                    
                  </tr>
                  <tr>
                    <td colspan="2">State: <u>
                        <t t-esc="state_name" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                    <td>Zip: <u>
                        <t t-esc="zip_code" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                    <td>Cell #: <u>
                        <t t-esc="mobile" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                    <td>Email: <u>
                        <t t-esc="email" />
                      </u>
                    </td>
                  </tr>
                </table>


                <p class="mt-3"> This Marketing Agreement (hereinafter referred to as the
                  “agreement”), made this date, by and between Westside Market LLC, a Georgia
                  corporation, (hereinafter referred to as “Westside”), and <t
                    t-esc="record.user_id.name" /> referred to as Consignor. </p>
              </div>
            </div>


            <div class="row text-center mt-3 mb-3">
              <div class="col-12">
                <h4>RECITALS</h4>
              </div>
            </div>

            <div class="row">
              <div class="col-12">
                <p>Whereas Consignor is engaged in the business of selling or consigning items such
                  as
                  antiques, collectibles, accessories, rugs, furniture, decorative arts, clothing,
                  and
                  other similar items related to interiors/design/apparel hereinafter referred to as
                  the
                  “merchandise”.</p>
                <p>Whereas, Westside has leased a building at 1530 Ellsworth Industrial Blvd., NW
                  Atlanta,
                  GA. 30318 to allow Consignor to display their merchandise, and</p>
                <p>Whereas, Consignor desires to appoint Westside as an independent sales agent and
                  Westside desires to become an independent sales agent of Consignor for merchandise
                  located at Westside according to the terms and conditions hereinafter set forth;</p>
              </div>

            </div>

            <div class="row  mt-3 mb-3">
              <div class="col-12 text-center">
                <h4>CONSIGNMENT, DISPLAY &amp; SALES AGREEMENT</h4>
              </div>
            </div>

            <div class="row">
              <div class="col-12">
                <p><strong>Term.</strong> This Agreement shall be for a term of six (6) months,
                  commencing on <t
                    t-esc="record.create_date.month == 1 and '1' or (record.create_date + relativedelta(day=1, months=1)).strftime('%B %d, %Y')" />
                  , <t t-esc="time.strftime('%Y')"></t> .</p>
                <p>This Agreement will automatically renew.</p>
              </div>
            </div>

            <div class="row">
              <div class="col-12">
                <p><strong>Agency.</strong> Consignor hereby appoints Westside as Consignor’s sales
                  agent to represent Consignor in the marketing and promotion of Consignor’s
                  merchandise located at Westside.</p>
              </div>
            </div>

            <div class="row">
              <div class="col-12">
                <p><strong>Assignment.</strong> Consignor shall not assign this Agreement or any
                  portion thereof, or allow a third party to use the space or any portion thereof,
                  nor subcontract or grant any third party the right to conduct any aspect of
                  Consignor’s business upon the space or the building.</p>
              </div>
            </div>

            <div class="row">
              <div class="col-12">
                <p><strong>Fees.</strong> Each Consignor will be charged a marketing fee for the
                  designated “space(s)” assigned. Consignor agrees to pay Westside the monthly
                  “Marketing Fee” payable on the first day of the month. Westside will have annual
                  increases on the 1st of Jan of every year, price increases are announced on Oct
                  1st every year.</p>
              </div>
            </div>


            <div class="row">
              <div class="col-12">
                <p>
                  Marketing fee is required to be set up as a recurring charge through our secured
                  credit card payment processing system. If payment is not received, your proceeds
                  payment for the prior sales month will not be issued.
                </p>
                <p>
                  Payment received after the 5th will incur a 10% late charge which will be applied
                  to the unpaid balance. Proceed checks will be available 7 days from the date the
                  account becomes current.
                </p>
                <p>
                  If the Marketing Fee is not paid by the 10th of the month in which it is due, the
                  contract will be considered void, and the Consignor will forfeit all deposits.
                  Consignor's merchandise will be removed from the showroom by the end of the month
                  and will incur a $50.00 per day storage fee until all monies due are paid.
                </p>
                <p>
                  Marketing fees are collected each month and will be used for the promotion of
                  Westside, including but not limited to advertising special events, promotional
                  materials, signage, and overhead, including costs associated with the daily
                  operations of Westside. There will be no refunds on marketing fees.
                </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Pallet Fee:</strong> You will be charged $20 a pallet received in the
                  Westside warehouse. It will be invoiced monthly. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Declined Marketing Fee Payments:</strong> Declined payments from
                  Consignors to Westside will incur a $50.00 reprocessing fee. It is the Consignor’s
                  responsibility to make sure their credit card has sufficient funds available and
                  is up to date. Proceed payments will be available 7 days from the date the account
                  becomes current. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Proceeds:</strong> Proceeds, less sales tax, fees of 4% for credit card
                  transactions, and Westside commission of 10% will be made on the 8th of the month
                  for the previous month’s activity. Your proceeds will be held if the rent, or any
                  assessed fees, including but not limited to late fees, insurance fees, freight or
                  delivery fees, etc., have not been paid on time. Lost checks will incur a $50.00
                  fee to reissue a new check. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Type of Merchandise:</strong> Consignor agrees that the only merchandise
                  to be sold in the designated space is to be defined below. (Please be specific and
                  detailed) </p>
                <p>
                  ____________________________________________________________________________________________________________
                  ____________________________________________________________________________________________________________
                  ____________________________________________________________________________________________________________
                  ____________________________________________________________________________________________________________
                </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Westside reserves the right to approve or disapprove any merchandise to be
                  sold.</strong> If merchandise does not meet with the approval of Westside
                  management, the Consignor will be advised in writing. Examples of merchandise that
                  are not acceptable are food, alcohol, counterfeit or knock-off merchandise,
                  defective or misrepresented items, and hazardous materials. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Non-approved merchandise must be removed from Consignor’s space within 2
                  business days.</strong> If Consignor has not removed the merchandise within 2
                  days, Westside will charge the Consignor $25.00 per hour, per person for labor
                  plus storage charges of $50.00 per day for the merchandise removed. If Westside
                  determines certain merchandise may present a hazard to our customers or employees,
                  it will be removed immediately. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>NEW categories of merchandise not listed by Consignor in this contract
                    must be approved by Westside management before being placed in the space in
                    writing.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Security Deposit:</strong> Consignor agrees to pay Westside a refundable
                  deposit equivalent to one month’s marketing fee payable on the date this agreement
                  is executed by Consignor. Westside shall receive and hold the security deposit
                  without liability for interest. </p>

                <p>
                  Security deposits will be returned to the Consignor subject to other provisions
                  within this contract by the 15th of the following month after you have vacated
                  your space.
                </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Premises Liability Insurance:</strong> is included in your monthly fee.
                  This insurance covers bodily injury or death to any person(s) because of any
                  negligent act, gross negligent act on the part of the Consignor, its employees, or
                  agents. Subject to policy terms, conditions, and exclusions. At no time will this
                  fee be prorated or refunded. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Property Insurance:</strong> is included in your monthly fee. This
                  insurance covers you for Fire, lightning wind, and smoke. Actual coverage will be
                  subject to the terms, conditions, limitations, limits, and sub-limits of the
                  policy. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Credit Card Fees:</strong> Credit card sales will be assessed a fee of
                  (4%) four percent. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Sales Tax:</strong> Westside collects and remits all state and local sales
                  tax. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Construction:</strong> Painting of walls is prohibited. Any construction
                  and/or floor coverings completed in and around the assigned space must be approved
                  by Westside in writing prior to commencing work. Any approved construction must be
                  completed by a licensed and insured general contractor. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>All improvements such as but not limited to walls, drywall, pegboard,
                    wood, or laminate flooring, electrical, or attachments will become the property
                    of Westside.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Any damages to your designated or surrounding space while building or
                  moving in or out shall be your responsibility and will be deducted from a paycheck
                  or deposit.</strong> Consignor shall not place any sign in or on the building,
                  including the space, without prior written approval of Westside. No permanent or
                  hazardous changes to the walls nor floors are allowed. Space must be returned to
                  its original condition subject to Westside’s discretion. Westside is not
                  responsible for injury or damages due to any construction made by the member. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Notice to Vacate:</strong> All notices to vacate must be in writing in an
                  email to the store manager and given to Westside 30 days or more prior to vacating
                  the space. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Failure to Vacate:</strong> If Consignor fails to vacate on the
                  agreed-upon termination date, each day thereafter will result in a $50.00 per day
                  storage fee. Should Westside have to move Consignor's merchandise to the
                  warehouse, a fee of $25.00 per hour per person will be charged. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>Merchandise:</strong> Consignor acknowledges that Westside has the right
                  to impose quality control restrictions on the merchandise and agrees to remove any
                  merchandise determined by Westside, at Westside’s sole discretion that does not
                  meet Westside’s standards. </p>
                <p>
                  <strong>CLAIM:</strong>
                </p>
                <ul>
                  <li><strong>Clean:</strong> Space is clean or customer-ready.</li>
                  <li><strong>Lighting:</strong> Having proper lighting.</li>
                  <li><strong>Accessibility:</strong> Customers can easily access and shop space.</li>
                  <li><strong>Inspiring:</strong> Make your space inviting with creativity, fresh
                    merchandise, and a unique look.</li>
                  <li><strong>Maintenance:</strong> Visit your space often, keep it stocked with new
                    merchandise.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                  <strong>Abandonment:</strong> Westside has the right to terminate Consignor's
                  agreement for abandonment of Consignor's designated space. This includes but is
                  not limited to an empty space, filth, and/or merchandise on the floor for lack of
                  furniture to place breakables. Payment of marketing fees does not exclude
                  Consignors from these standards. If the Consignor fails to correct the situation
                  within the 30 days, the agreement may be terminated by Westside. No deposit will
                  be refunded. Any merchandise, display fixtures, shelving, or property left on the
                  premises of Westside after Consignor has paid final fees and/or termination of
                  this agreement by any action shall be considered abandoned and may be sold or
                  disposed of by Westside at Westside’s discretion. </p>


                <p><strong>Sales Policy.</strong> All sales or special orders from Consignor’s space
                  must go through Westside Market's register. NO sales will be permitted directly to
                  customers. Any violations of this policy will be a default of your contract and
                  would cause a termination of your contract.</p>

                <p><strong>Hazardous Materials.</strong> No hazardous materials are allowed at
                  Westside. Consignor represents and warrants that it will operate on the premises
                  in compliance with any and all Federal, State, or local laws, rules, or
                  ordinances.</p>

                <p><strong>Termination.</strong> Westside has the right to retain your deposit and
                  terminate your agreement for the following reasons: Failure to move into Westside
                  after signing an agreement, failure to provide the required notice when vacating,
                  failure to fulfill the agreement terms, excessive late marketing fee payments,
                  bounced checks, a significant change to unacceptable merchandise or insufficient
                  merchandise, failure to run sales through Westside, failure to maintain your space
                  in accordance with Westside policies, or maintain your space a minimum of once a
                  week.</p>

                <p>All Consignors of Westside, including their principals and employees, must
                  conduct themselves at all times in a professional manner. Any disputes that may
                  arise between or among other Consignors regarding product offerings or any other
                  issue must immediately be brought to the attention of Westside management. Any
                  violation of this section may result in termination of the marketing agreement.</p>

                <strong>
                  <p>General:</p>
                </strong>
                <ol>
                  <li>Please return Westside Market phone calls &amp; emails ASAP for your benefit.</li>
                  <li>Consignors must notify Westside Market management 24 hours in advance when
                    merchandise is being shipped to be received at Westside Market dock.</li>
                  <li>Consignors must remove shipments received by Westside Market to their space
                    within 48 hours.</li>
                  <li>Consignors are expected to bring any merchandise in and out of their locations
                    with their own manpower.</li>
                  <li>Consignors must sign in &amp; out every time you visit the Westside Market
                    front desk when entering &amp; leaving the Market.</li>
                  <li>Consignors are permitted to bring small furniture and accessories through the
                    front entry. Large items are to be brought through the warehouse access located
                    in the rear of the store.</li>
                  <li>Consignors must notify their store manager via email for any personnel who
                    will be removing items from their space. This includes delivery persons or
                    delivery companies.</li>
                </ol>

                <strong>
                  <p>Tagging of Merchandise:</p>
                </strong>
                <ol>
                  <li>Each Consignor must enter their inventory with descriptions and pricing into
                    Westside’s POS SYSTEM.</li>
                  <li>You can print your Labels or can be printed by Westside and given to the
                    members. It is the member’s responsibility to tag their own products with
                    Westside’s labels.</li>
                  <li>ALL items must be tagged securely with Westside's Tags. Consignor’s code, item
                    #, item description (description to be accurate, real, and true).</li>
                  <li>We are not responsible for mis-tagged, mislabeled, or illegible tags on
                    merchandise.</li>
                  <li>Any items NOT for sale in your space must be tagged DISPLAY ONLY-NOT FOR SALE.</li>
                  <li>Westside encourages consignors to impart product knowledge to our sales team
                    to better serve our customers and be a better representative of your product.</li>
                  <li>Any damaged merchandise must be tagged AS-IS along with what the damage is
                    and/or any missing pieces listed.</li>
                  <li>Items hung high, over 6ft, MUST have a large enough tag to be read and if
                    needed information placed low enough to read.</li>
                  <li>Clearance and sale signs MUST be approved, produced and hung by Westside
                    management before being placed in space.</li>
                </ol>

                <p><strong>Sales Policy.</strong> All sales or special orders from Consignor’s space
                  must go through the Westside register. NO sales will be permitted directly to
                  customers. Any violations of this policy will be a default of your contract and
                  would cause a termination of your contract.</p>

                <p><strong>Discounting of Merchandise.</strong> We offer discounts to registered
                  trade/interior designers. Each Consignor can choose from 10% and up as a trade
                  discount. ALL SALE ITEMS MUST BE MARKED “FIRM” IF YOU DO NOT WISH FURTHER
                  DISCOUNTS TO BE TAKEN.</p>

                <p><strong>Sales &amp; Special Events.</strong> Westside will conduct store SALES
                  Events several times a year. Enough notice will be given so each Consignor can
                  prepare their booth and inventory. Member sales must be requested in writing via
                  email to the store. Sale requests must follow store guidelines. Westside will have
                  special events planned throughout the year. Consignors are encouraged to be
                  present and have their booth staffed. Consignors are also encouraged to actively
                  participate in promotional activities that will enhance sales and community
                  awareness. It is important to the success of everyone’s business for everyone to
                  be involved. Please see Westside Market management with any ideas or
                  opportunities.</p>

                <p><strong>Film and Photography Rental.</strong> We offer merchandise rentals to
                  film and photography production companies. Film/Photography rentals are charged
                  25% of the original selling price for a two-week period (not the sales price).</p>

                <p><strong>Display of Space.</strong> Westside's mission is to offer the trade and
                  public a unique &amp; design-oriented visual experience when walking through
                  Westside Market. Each Consignor must strive to maintain this experience through
                  upscale merchandised spaces. Westside will make sure as items sell empty spaces
                  will be filled. It is each Consignor's responsibility to make sure weekly
                  restocking is done.</p>

                <p>Merchandise must be kept in the parameters of each Consignor’s space. No items in
                  aisles, no items stacked up like a warehouse. NO merchandise is to be hung on the
                  outside end caps unless you have rented said Endcap. End cap shelves can’t exceed
                  6 inches in depth and 2 feet off the ground.</p>

                <p>Merchandise must be ready to sell when brought onto premises. No repairing,
                  painting, or refinishing of the product is to be done in or around the building.</p>

                <p>Consignors must provide their supplies such as nails, screws, hammers, tape, etc.
                  Westside will not provide any tools or supplies. Westside provides ladders and
                  carts to be used at your risk.</p>

                <p>When re-merchandising your space, be respectful of fellow Consignors by not
                  blocking aisles or placing items in front of their space.</p>

                <p><strong>Electrical.</strong> All lighting must be LED. Max allowable wattage
                  equals the total wattage of all bulbs used in a space: Single Booth 15 watts, 1.5
                  Booth 23 watts, Double Booth 30 watts, Triple Booth 45 watts. Extension cords
                  should be hidden and kept to a minimum. All visible extension cords and those that
                  could cause harm to customers will be removed without notice.</p>

                <p><strong>Lost, Stolen or Damaged Merchandise.</strong> Westside will make all
                  reasonable effort to protect Consignor's merchandise from loss, theft, or damage.
                  Under normal business activities, Consignors and Westside Market management
                  recognize that items may be stolen, lost, or damaged. Both parties accept this as
                  a normal cost of doing business. Members understand it is their choice and
                  responsibility to maintain insurance for property located in their booths.</p>

                <p>In the event that Westside damages a Consignor’s merchandise, Westside reserves
                  the right to repair the merchandise to the original condition if appropriate. If
                  Westside is unable to make such repairs, Westside will reimburse the Consignor’s
                  cost of the item (not the retail price) once an invoice is submitted. Those items
                  then become the property of Westside Market.</p>

                <p><strong>Advertising.</strong> We encourage you to link your website, Facebook,
                  Instagram accounts, and other social media to Westside website, Facebook,
                  Instagram, and other social media. Any Consignor is welcome to participate in
                  Westside advertising programs, home shows, and outside special events through
                  their advertising channels. Please see management for more details.</p>

                <p><strong>Breach of Contract.</strong> In the event of a breach of this Agreement,
                  including but not limited to nonpayment of marketing fees, late payment of
                  marketing fees, or any other breach of this Agreement, Westside shall have the
                  right to immediately terminate this Agreement, claim possession of any and all of
                  Consignor's merchandise, lock up or remove Consignor's merchandise, sell
                  Consignor's merchandise to satisfy unpaid marketing fees, and exercise all other
                  remedies to Westside in accordance with the laws of the State of Georgia.</p>

                <p><strong>Subordination. </strong>In the event of the expiration or termination
                  (for any reason whatsoever) of the term of the superior lease between the owner of
                  the building and Westside, this Agreement shall automatically terminate. This
                  Agreement is subject and subordinate to the superior lease between the owner of
                  the building and Westside.</p>

                <p><strong>Amendments: </strong> Westside reserves the right to amend any provision
                  of this contract with 30 days written notice.</p>

                <p><strong>Legal Construction.</strong> Should any one or more of the provisions
                  contained within this Agreement be, for any reason, held invalid, illegal, or
                  unenforceable in any respect, such invalidation, illegality, or unenforceability
                  shall not affect any other provisions of the Agreement.</p>

                <p>I have read and understand the guidelines above as well as the “Policies and
                  Procedures'' of Westside and agree to follow them while being a Consignor with
                  Westside. IN WITNESS WHEREOF, each of the parties hereto has executed this
                  Agreement, all on the day and year first above written.</p>


                <p>
                  Consignor Signature: __________________________________ Date:
                  ______________________________________________
                </p>
                <p>
                  Consignor Print Name: __________________________________ Date:
                  ______________________________________________
                </p>


                <p> Westside Signature: <img style="width:250px"
                    t-att-src="image_data_uri(env['res.users'].sudo().search([('id','=',2)],limit=1).sign_signature)"></img>
                  Date: ________________________________ </p>
                <p> Westside Printed Name: <u>
                    <t t-out="user.name" />
                  </u> Date:
                  ______________________________________________ </p>


                <h2 class="mt-5 mb-5">Consignor Information</h2>
                <p> Consignor Name: <span>_____</span>[ Field by member]<span>_____________</span>
                  Consignor Tag ID: <span>__</span> [Field by member] ___ </p>
                <p>
                  This information will be kept on file for Westside sales staff &amp; management to
                  refer to as necessary. Any changes must be made in writing and sent to your store
                  manager email. Please allow up to 5 days for changes to be updated.
                </p>
                <ol>
                  <li> Allow customers to take merchandise out on approval? <br /> Yes <span>
                    _____________</span> No <span>__________</span>
                  </li>
                  <li> Allow film and photography production companies to take merchandise out for
                    rental? <br /> Yes <span>__________</span> No <span>__________</span>
                            <br />
                    Film/Photography Rentals are charged 25% of the original selling price for a
                    two-week period. </li>
                  <li> Allow a Trade Discount to registered designers? <br /> 10%_<span>__________</span>
                    15%_<span>__________</span> 20%_<span>__________</span> 25%_<span>__________</span>
                    30%_<span>__________</span> No <span>__________</span>
                  </li>
                  <li> Allow Westside to offer customers a minimum discount of 10% or more to make a
                    sale? <br /> 10%_<span>__________</span> 15%_<span>__________</span> 20%_<span>
                    __________</span> 25%_<span>__________</span> 30%_<span>__________</span> No <span>
                    __________</span>
                            <br /> Any further discount will have to contact you for
                    approval. </li>
                  <li> Accept Text Messages or Phone Calls regarding offers on your merchandise? <br />
                    Yes <span>__________</span> No <span>___________</span> Cell #: <span>
                    ___________</span>
                  </li>
                  <li> Allow Westside to utilize merchandise for front window vignettes? <br /> Yes <span>
                    __________</span> No <span>__________</span>
                  </li>
                </ol>
                <p> Consignor Signature: <span>_____________________________________</span> Date: <span>
                  ______________________</span>
                </p>


                <strong class="mt-2 mb-2">
                  <p class="o_p">CONSIGNMENT, DISPLAY &amp; SALES AGREEMENT</p>
                </strong>
                <p class="o_p">What you will be paying for today is:</p>
                <p class="o_p">$____________________= First month marketing fee.</p>
                <p class="o_p">$____________________= Deposit equal to one month marketing fee.</p>
                <p class="o_p">$____________________= Total due</p>
                <p class="o_p">Please fill out the information below for your recurring monthly
                  charges</p>
                <p class="o_p">Check One: MasterCard __________Visa___________ American
                  Express___________</p>
                <p class="o_p">Name on Card: _____________________________</p>
                <p class="o_p">Card Number:
                  __________________________________________________________</p>
                <p class="o_p">Expiration Date: ________________________ CVV Code: ________________
                  Zip Code: _________________</p>
                <p class="o_p">You authorize Westside to bill your credit card monthly for your
                  monthly marketing fee.</p>
                <p class="o_p">Signature: __________________________________________________________</p>
                <p class="o_p">Insurance Information</p>
                <p class="o_p">What is the total wholesale cost to replace the merchandise you plan
                  on having in your space at any one time? $___________________________</p>
                <p class="o_p">Signature ______________________________</p>
                <strong class="text-center mt-3">
                  <h2 class="o_p">WELCOME TO WESTSIDE MARKET MIDTOWN!!</h2>
                </strong>
              </div>
            </div>
          </div>
      

        </t>
      </t>
    </t>
  </template>

  <template id="contract_pdf">
    <t t-call="web.html_container">
      <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
        <t t-call="bmb_templates.bmb_contract" t-lang="doc.partner_id.lang" />
      </t>
    </t>
  </template>

</odoo>